[Music]
nobody likes you you girl well you're a
different color than me and that's bad
oh yeah when you dress like I'll hold on
a second whoa mr. t never make fun of
the way a man dresses wait a man dresses
is his business remember that whether
it's overalls chains or feather ear is
however they dress it's not to be joked
about I pity the fool that judges
another man's clothing I'm sorry I judge
your clothing
it's okay hey Scout there's a man over
there who said he'll give us candy if we
get in his van I don't know if that's a
good idea Timmy what are you afraid of
is it because you have a stupid name
like Scout hey whoa mr. t again never
make fun of a person's name your mama
gave you that name or you made it up for
business purposes
either way it's personal I pity the fool
to make fun of another man's name mr.
T's a cool name it's a cool name mr. T
[Music]
hey scout
why don't you some drugs aren't drugs
bad I don't know if you're afraid of
drugs we could drink a bunch of alcohol
YUM that sounds good
well guess what your hair is stupid
never make fun of another person's hair
hey mr. t a person's hair is the artwork
that they present to the heavens just
like I've been saying
[Music]
like the way I feel shots that take
and for your information it's not even a
haircut it's a rare form of male pattern
baldness you fools
[Music]